fotofuze.com 2012-10-02

# Privacy Policy | FotoFuze

## Privacy Policy

For information not covered below, please see the Terms of Service.

## Information We Collect

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and clear gifs to create a "profile" of your preferences. Personally identifiable information is used by FotoFuze in order to provide tailored services and to improve the content of the site for you. 

## Who We Share Information With

FotoFuze will comply with demands made by law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation.

Only NON-personally identifiable information may be shared or sold to FotoFuze partners.

## Who We Do Not Share Information With

We absolutely do NOT share your personally identifiable information (email address, first or last name, etc.) with ANY third-party or partner unless you explicitly request that we do.

## Customer Service

Based upon the information you provide us, we will send you a welcome email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, to manage your account and inform you of new services and features FotoFuze is offering. Any time that we email you, you will have the ability to opt out of all future communications.

FotoFuze will never ask for your login or personally identifiable information in emails, instant messages, or pop-ups. If you witness any of these possible scams, ignore them and inform us at support [at] fotofuze.com.

We take your privacy _very_ seriously; if you feel FotoFuze is violating your privacy in any way, please contact us at support [at] fotofuze.com

Last updated December 6, 2009
